// Quiz questions
const questions = [
{ 
    prompt: "Q1. What is the purpose of the HTML <head> element?", 
    options: [ 
        "To define the document's body", 
        "To contain metadata about the document",
        "To create a new section in the document",
        "To display text content",
    ], 
    answer: "To contain metadata about the document", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q2. Which CSS property is used to change the text colour of an element?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'font-colour\'", 
        "\'text-colour\'", 
        "\'colour\'",
        "\'font-style\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'colour\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q3. How do you declare a variable in JavaScript?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'new variable myVar;\'", 
        "\'var myVar;\'", 
        "\'variable myVar;\'",
        "\'let myVar;\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'var myVar;\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q4.Which HTML element is used to create a dropdown list?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'<select>\'", 
        "\'<input type=\"dropdown\">'", 
        "\'<dropdown>'",
        "\'<list>\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'<select>\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q5. What does the CSS property \'margin: 10px 20px 15px 5px;\' represent?", 
    options: [ 
        "Top, right, bottom, left margins in pixels", 
        "Top margin in pixels, right margin in em, bottom margin in percentage, left margin in rem", 
        "All margins are set to the same value of 10px", 
        "Incorrect CSS syntax", 
    ], 
    answer: "Top, right, bottom, left margins in pixels", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q6. How do you call a function named \'myFunction\' in JavaScript?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'call myFunction()\'", 
        "\'myFunction()\'", 
        "\'call function myFunction\'",
        "\'Call.myFunction\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'myFunction()\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q7. Which HTML element is used to define the structure of an HTML document, such as headings, paragraphs, and lists?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'<container>\'", 
        "\'<layout>\'", 
        "\'<structure>\'",
        "\'<body>\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'<body>\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q8. What CSS property is used to create a flexible box layout in a container?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'box-layout\'", 
        "\'display: flexbox\'", 
        "\'flex-direction\'",
        "\'layout: flex\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'flex-direction\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q9. How do you access the element at index 2 in a JavaScript array named \'myArray\'?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'myArray[2]\'", 
        "\'myArray.getElement(2)\'", 
        "\'myArray.getElementAtIndex(2)\'",
        "\'myArray.element(2)\'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'myArray[2]\'", 
},

{ 
    prompt: "Q10. Which HTML5 element is used to play video files?", 
    options: [ 
        "\'<media>\'", 
        "\'<video>\'", 
        "\'<play>\'",
        "\'<movie>'",
    ], 
    answer: "\'<video>\'", 
},
];


